

17F-4, No.17, Ln.175, Wuling Rd., Hsinchu City, Taiwan (R.O.C.)

🛮 (+886) 916-242-713 | 🗷 cwhuangb1321@gmail.com | 🏕 hannnnk1231.github.io | 🖸 hannnnk1231 | 🛅 minghanhuang | 📢 hannnnk1231

Summary _

I'm Hank Huang, currently a 1st year M.S. student in Institute of **Data Science and Engineering at National Chiao Tung University**. My current research interest is in **Data Science, Machine Learning and Deep Learning**. Having an in-depth knowledge including advanced **Python, Keras** and **C/C++**. I perform very good **self-learning** and **team work** abilities. I aim to make a difference through my creative and **effective** solution. In addition, my interests are photography, vlog and magic.

Education

National Chiao Tung University

HsinChu, Taiwar

M.S. IN DATA SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING, GPA: 4.1/4.3

Sep. 2019 - present

- Lab: Learning Science and Technology Lab, Advisior: Prof. Chuen-Tsai Sun
- Courses: Machine Learning, Data Minging, Data Visualization and Visual Analytics, Computer Vision(Ongoing), NLP(Ongoing).
- Teaching Assistant: Game-based Digital Learning

National Taiwan University

Taipei, Taiwan

B.S. IN MATHEMATICS

Sep. 2014 - Jun. 2018

 Relevant Courses (Provided by NTU CS department): Algorithm, Data Structure, Discrete Mathematics, Human-Computer Interaction, Virtual Reality

Work Experience

Fellow, Turing Chain Institution

Taiwai

ACCEPTANCE RATE 4.5%

Sep. 2019 - Jan. 2020

- · Working with team on backend develop using JavaScript, NodeJS and NestJS in a blockchain project
- Self-learning blockchain technology from 0 to 1 in just one month

R.O.C Army

Taiwan

MICROFILM SPECIAL TEAM

Mar. 2019 - Jul. 2019

· Train as a soilder.

Research Assistant, National Taiwan University of Science and Technology, Game Lab

Taipei, Taiwan May. 2018 - Dec. 2018

PROJECT: AUTOMATIC LICENSE PLATE RECOGNITION, ADVISOR: PROF. WEN-KAI TAI

• Proposed to use YOLOv3, image processing for automatic license plate recognition and flow count, result 98%up accuracy.

• Integrate API from backend and maintaining code using C++ and Python

PROJECT: Al GAMING [1], ADVISOR: WEN-KAI TAI

- Design a system for procedurally generating Pac-Man maze with specified difficulty
- Proposed a Pac-Man level quality checking methods using esthetic score.

Honors & Awards

2019 **Top 1000**, Kick Start 2019 Round G

Online

2019 **Top 11%**, Kaggle Digit Recognizer competition

Online

2019 Rank 10(Top 1%), Kaggle Kannada MNIST competition

Online

Publications.

1. Z. Wu, K. Lai, L. Lin, **M. Huang** and W. Tai, "Procedurally Generating Game Level with Specified Difficulty," 2018 IEEE Games, Entertainment, Media Conference (GEM 2018)

Certificates

2019 IBM , Data Science Specializa

Online

2019 **IBM**, Machine Learning with Python

Online

2019 **NVIDIA**, Deep Learning foundamental

Online

Extracurricular Activity

Director, National Taiwan University Magic Club

TEAM WORK AND PUBLIC RELATION

Jun. 2016 - Jun. 2017

Minister of Artistic Design Department, Student Association of Mathematics Department

Mar. 2015 - Jun. 2016

• Designing poster and program list for public performance and events

• Develop/Maintaining Facebook fan page

• Lead club members for grand shows

Skills

Natural Languages Chinese(Mandarin), English(**TOEFL iBT:87**)

Programming Python, SQL, C/C++, Solidity, LTEX

Deep Learning Libraries Tensorflow, Keras

Creativity Photoshop, Final Cut Pro, Lightroom, After Effects